

# **EDUCATION**

### **DIPLOMA IN ANIMATIONS**

WIZTOONZ 2014-2018

### B.A

HIMALAYAN University 2015-2018

# REFERENCE

# **Vibhas**

Manager I Eagleview T: +91 9535450167

# Arun M

Team Leader I Eagleview T:+91 8553874889

# Mobile

+91 9740825166

### **Email**

harish640630@gmail.com

# Address

No.15 GRS layout Gunjur,Bengaluru 560087

# HARISH N SENIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER

# INTRODUCTION

'Senior graphic design specialist with more than 5 years of experience in managing graphic design projects from inception to execution. Highly creative with the ability to work well within a team. Extensive experience in managing other designers and coordinating with them to deliver a single product. Highly skilled with various programs within the Adobe Creative Suite.'

### WORK EXPERIENCE

2023-April SR.GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Swipewire Technologies Private Limited / Chennai

▶ Banner Design. ▶ Logo Design. ▶ Weblayout Design.

▶ Photo Manipulation. ▶ Brand Identity. ▶ Social Media Posters.

2021-2022 PHOTOGRAMMETRIC CORRECTION TECHNICIAN

Eagleview / Bengaluru

▶ Color correction. ▶ Photo Manipulation. ▶ Image Editor.

▶ Aerial Image Editing. ▶ Project Management.

2018-2020 GRAPHIC DESIGNER ( CONSULTANT)

CMS IT SERVICES / Bengaluru

▶ Social Media Posters. ▶ Brand Identity. ▶ Banner Design.

▶ Logo Design. ▶ Gif Animation. ▶ Video Editor.

2016-2018 PACKAGING DESIGNER

PAGARIYA Pvt.Ltd / Bengaluru

▶ Packeging Design. ▶ Logo Design. ▶ Banner Design.

▶ Social Media Posters. ▶ Brand Identity. ▶ Mockup.

# SOFTWARE SKILL

Adobe photoshop

Adobe After Effects

Adobe Lightroom

Adobe Premiere Pro

Adobe Adution

MS Word Powerpoint